This video introduces the new feature of Closet.
This season, we have released a series of new features
that make it easy for users to check 3D clothing on Closet.
One of the important updates is the 2D version of the viewfinder.
Just like in the Closet software,
users can check the 2D paper in the 3D file on Closet.
On the left side, click on the shrink chart of the 2D window
to display the 2D paper.
Just like Closet,
users can change the display options through the 2D menu.
For example, we can display the kill line direction
and check if all the kill line directions are correctly set.
In addition,
we can add views directly in the 2D viewfinder
to add comments or record any necessary modifications.
If you do not need to use the 2D viewfinder,
you can use this option.
Click on the settings button under the company layer.
In the general settings, you can see that
the 2D version of the viewfinder is activated.
Then click to stop it.
After you click on it,
you can notice the shrink chart of the 2D version of the viewfinder.
In the 3D clothing viewfinder, you cannot see
the shrink chart of the 2D version of the viewfinder.
Even if you are an inexperienced user,
you can check the 2D version of the viewfinder online.
We also released a 3D quality check tool
for automatically detecting the attribute settings of 3D clothing.
To use this function,
we must activate it first.
Under the company file layer,
click on the settings button.
Find the content in the navigation bar.
Select 3D quality check.
It is currently in the state of active.
Click to activate it.
To check the quality of the 3D file created in the hole,
you can set the standard according to the specific requirements.
For example, we can set the particle diameter to 3-5.
Find here and enter 3-5.
And set the clothing to close the hardening function.
After the setting is complete,
click on the application about how to configure the check chart
and more detailed information to check the results.
You can click on the PDF guide in the upper right corner.
You can access the PDF guide here
to learn more details.
After setting the quality check standard,
upload the 3D clothing to be quality checked.
On the left side of the content page, you can see the QC mark.
Click on it.
Click on the QC mark in the content page.
If the property is in line with the standard,
it will be marked as green.
If not, it will be marked as red.
You can click on the check mark.
To check in detail which specific parts of the file are not in line with the standard.
In this way,
you can check the quality of the 3D clothing in the close set.
You can simplify the workflow more efficiently.
Next, let's look at the 3D clothing.
Next, let's look at the QC mark.
QC managers can check the quality of the 3D clothing
in a more efficient way than before.
QC managers can activate the QC mark in advance.
On the left side of the control panel,
click on the QC setting.
Click on the QC mark.
After clicking on this option,
when the existing users in the working area
invite new users to enter the working area,
they must first obtain the approval of the QC manager,
in order to complete the process.
For example,
when the existing users invite other users as observers
to enter the working area,
the required users will be marked as pre-checked.
In this process,
QC managers will receive email notifications
and check accordingly.
To continue to check,
QC managers can click on the user history record
on the control panel on the left side.
Select the full line check option,
and then click on the QC mark.
Under the pre-checked users,
QC managers can choose to agree or reject users.
By using this function,
QC managers can fully master the invitation details in the group,
to achieve higher security
and better control of subscription costs.